("L'AMOUR DE MA VIE"
BY BILLIE EILISH FADING IN)
(ELECTRICAL BUZZ)
(BUZZES, WHOOSHES)
("L'AMOUR DE MA VIE" PLAYS)
(WHOOSHING)
(CLINKING)
("L'AMOUR DE MA VIE" CONTINUES)
(RIGGING CREAKING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(ELECTRONIC THRUMMING)
(SCREAMS)
(THRUMMING CONTINUES)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
(THRUMMING CONTINUES)
BILLIE:
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
Whoo!
(HEAVY ELECTRONIC TONE)
(CHEERING)
Oh, my God!
(MELODY OF
"THE GREATEST" PLAYS)
(HEAVY TONES, MELODY CONTINUE)
(CHEERS ERUPT)
(SQUEALS)
(GIRL SCREAMS)
Oh, my God!
(ECSTATIC LAUGHTER)
(SQUEALING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(AUDIENCE ROARS)
(DELIGHTED SCREAM)
(YELPS, LAUGHS)
("CHIHIRO" PLAYS)
♪ To take my love away ♪
♪ When I come back around
Will I know what to say? ♪
♪ Said you won't forget
My name ♪
♪ Not today ♪
(AUDIENCE SINGING ALONG)
♪ Not tomorrow ♪
♪ Kinda strange ♪
♪ Feelin' sorrow ♪
♪ I got change ♪
♪ You could borrow ♪
♪ When I come back around
Will I know what to say? ♪
♪ Not today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow ♪
♪ Open up the door
Can you open up the door? ♪
♪ I know you said before
You can't cope with anymore ♪
♪ You told me it was war
You'd show me what's in store ♪
♪ I hope it's not for sure
Can you open up the... ♪
♪ Did you ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Take ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ From me? ♪
♪ Me ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Saw your seat at the counter
When I looked away ♪
♪ Saw you turn around
But it wasn't your face ♪
♪ Said, "I need to be alone now
I'm takin' a break" ♪
♪ How come when I returned,
You were gone away? ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ I don't, I don't know ♪
♪ Why I called ♪
♪ I don't know you at all ♪
♪ I don't ♪
♪ Know you ♪
♪ I don't, I don't know ♪
♪ Why I called ♪
♪ I don't know you at all ♪
♪ I don't know you ♪
♪ Did you ♪
♪ Take ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ Away ♪
From who?
AUDIENCE:
♪ From me ♪
♪ Me ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ And that's when
You found me ♪
♪ I was waitin' in the garden ♪
♪ Contemplatin' ♪
♪ I beg your pardon ♪
♪ But there's a part of me
That recognizes you ♪
♪ Do you feel it too? ♪
♪ When you told me
It was serious ♪
♪ Were you serious? ♪
Hmm?
♪ They told me
They were only curious ♪
♪ But now it's serious ♪
Uh-huh.
AUDIENCE: ♪ Open up the door
Can you open up the door? ♪
♪ I know you said before
You can't cope with anymore ♪
♪ You told me it was war ♪
♪ Said you'd show me
What's in store ♪
♪ I hope it's not for sure ♪
♪ Can you open up the door? ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Wringing my hands in my lap ♪
♪ And they tell me
It's all been a trap ♪
♪ And you don't know
If you'll make it back ♪
♪ I said
"No, don't say that" ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ You don't know
If you'll make it back ♪
♪ But I said,
"No, don't say that" ♪
♪ Wringing my hands in my lap ♪
♪ You tell me
It's all been a trap ♪
♪ You don't know
If you'll make it back ♪
♪ Don't say that ♪
(MUSIC STOPS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
I love you!
(CHEERING FADES)
(HUMMING)
BILLIE: All right.
Here I go.
WOMAN: Yeah, we're cool.
MAN: And we're rolling?
ALL: One, two, three...
3D!
(CHEERING)
See you out there.
CREWMAN: You're a star.
(MIMICKING ACCENT)
Have a great show, darling.
CREWMAN:
Great show, Billie darling.
Babes.
Go on, darling.
You all right?
BILLIE: Yeah.
Yeah, let's do it.
CREWMAN: It's show time.
Yeah.
CREWMAN 2:
Good luck, everyone.
(DISTANT CHEERS, CROWD MURMURS)
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
All right, everybody.
Stand by
for start of show in...
five, four, three, two, one.
Go!
(DISTANT CHEERING)
(ELECTRONIC THRUMMING)
(HARNESS CLINKING)
(HEAVY ELECTRONIC TONE)
("LUNCH" PLAYS)
♪ I could eat that girl
For lunch ♪
♪ She dances on my tongue ♪
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
♪ And I could
Never get enough ♪
♪ I could buy her
So much stuff ♪
♪ It's a craving, not a crush ♪
♪ "Call me when you're there" ♪
♪ "I bought you somethin' rare
I left it under" ♪
♪ "Claire" ♪
♪ So now she's comin'
Up the stairs ♪
♪ I'm pullin' up a chair ♪
♪ I'm puttin' up my hair ♪
♪ Baby, I think
You were made for me ♪
♪ Somebody write down
The recipe ♪
♪ Been tryin' hard
Not to overeat ♪
What?
AUDIENCE:
♪ You're just so sweet ♪
♪ I'll run a shower for you
Like you want ♪
♪ Clothes on the counter
For you ♪
♪ Try 'em on ♪
♪ If I'm allowed,
I'll help you take 'em off ♪
Come on!
(CHEERING)
♪ I could eat that girl
For lunch ♪
♪ She dances on my ♪
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
♪ And I could
Never get enough ♪
♪ I could buy her
So much stuff ♪
♪ It's a craving, not a crush ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ She's takin' pictures
In the mirror ♪
♪ My God, her skin's so clear ♪
♪ "Come bring that over" ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ "Here" ♪
♪ You need a seat?
I'll volunteer ♪
♪ Now she's smilin'
Ear to ear ♪
♪ She's the headlights
I'm the deer ♪
♪ I've said it all before
But I'll say it again ♪
♪ I'm interested in more
Than just being a friend ♪
♪ I don't wanna break it ♪
♪ Just want it to bend ♪
♪ Do you know how to bend ♪
♪ I could eat that girl
For lunch ♪
♪ She dances on my tongue ♪
♪ I know it's just a hunch ♪
♪ But she might be the one ♪
Come on!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
♪ I could ♪
♪ Eat that girl for lunch ♪
♪ Yeah, she ♪
(RHYTHMIC STOMPING)
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
♪ I could ♪
♪ Eat that girl for lunch ♪
Whoo!
♪ Yeah, she ♪
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
("NDA" PLAYS)
♪ Did you think
I'd show up in a limousine? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Had to save my money
For security ♪
♪ Got a stalker walkin'
Up and down the street ♪
♪ Says he's Satan ♪
♪ And he'd like to meet ♪
♪ I bought a secret house
When I was seventeen ♪
♪ Haven't had a party
Since I got the keys ♪
♪ Had a pretty boy over
But he couldn't stay ♪
♪ On his way out
Made him sign an NDA ♪
♪ Mm ♪
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(HUMMING ALONG)
♪ Yeah, I made him
Sign an NDA ♪
♪ Once was good enough ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't want him
Havin' shit to say ♪
♪ Hm-mm-mm ♪
♪ You couldn't save me ♪
♪ But you can't ♪
♪ Let me ♪
♪ Go ♪
♪ I can crave you ♪
♪ But you don't need ♪
♪ To know ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Did I take it too far? ♪
♪ Now I know what you are ♪
♪ You hit me so hard ♪
♪ That I saw stars ♪
♪ Think I took it too far ♪
♪ When I sold you my heart ♪
♪ How'd it get so dark? ♪
♪ I saw stars ♪
♪ Stars ♪
(MUSIC TRANSITIONS
TO "THEREFORE I AM")
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(CHEERING)
♪ I'm not your friend ♪
(FLAMES ROAR)
♪ Or anything
Damn ♪
♪ You think
That you're the man ♪
♪ I think, therefore, I am ♪
♪ I'm not your friend ♪
♪ Or anything
Damn ♪
♪ You think
That you're the man ♪
♪ I think, therefore, I am ♪
♪ Stop ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ What the hell
Are you talking about? ♪
BILLIE: ♪ Get my pretty name
Out of your mouth ♪
♪ We are not the same
With or without ♪
♪ Don't talk 'bout me like ♪
♪ How you might know
How I feel ♪
♪ Top of the world,
But your world isn't real ♪
♪ Your world's an ideal ♪
♪ So go have fun ♪
♪ I really couldn't care less ♪
♪ And you can give 'em
My best ♪
♪ But just know ♪
♪ I'm not your friend ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Or anything
Damn ♪
♪ You think that
You're the man ♪
♪ I think, therefore, I am ♪
♪ I'm not your friend ♪
♪ Or anything
Damn ♪
♪ You think
That you're the man ♪
♪ I think, therefore, I am ♪
♪ I don't want press to put
Your name next to mine ♪
♪ We're on different lines
So I ♪
♪ Wanna be nice enough
They don't call my bluff ♪
♪ 'Cause I hate to find ♪
What?
AUDIENCE: ♪ Articles
Articles, articles ♪
♪ Rather you remain
Unremarkable ♪
♪ Got a lotta ♪
♪ Interviews, interviews ♪
♪ When they say your name
I just act confused ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Did you have fun?
I really couldn't care less ♪
♪ And you can give 'em my best
But just know ♪
♪ I'm not your friend
Or anything ♪
♪ Damn ♪
♪ You think that you're ♪
♪ I think therefore ♪
♪ I am ♪
♪ I'm not your friend ♪
♪ Damn ♪
♪ You think
That you're the man ♪
♪ I think, therefore, I am ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Oh, my goodness.
JAMES: Oh, my goodness!
Look who it is!
Hello, Jimothy.
Hi, I'm coming in filming.
Which you would expect.
I couldn't possibly
not see that.
Bring it in.
Oh, hi. I didn't know
what you were doing.
I was like, "Oh, hi, Jim".
Do you mind, for a second,
just talk about
your creative process.
Like, what went into
the creation of the--
of the show?
("THE GREATEST"
PLAYING FAINTLY)
JAMES:
I see this as your show.
You are the architect
of this show.
You knew what you wanted.
BILLIE:
Ever since the beginning,
like, the people that
I've been working with
have really been
very receptive to my ideas.
And they've truly just
listened to me for many years,
and it feels really nice
to have that.
And every single tour
since I started, I--
I sit down
with the lighting techs
and we go over what color
every single song is.
It's so important to me
that the songs at the concert
envelop you
in all of the senses
that it possibly can.
Almost like the best kind
of sensory overload
that you can get.
JAMES: Yeah.
BILLIE: You know?
(BEATS ECHOING
OVER SOUND SYSTEM)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
That's James Cameron.
Yeah.
It comes down
and this is a part of it.
Yeah.
And then it goes off.
It would be really cool
for everyone to see
my experience in that.
(MURMURS, CHUCKLES)
Two thumbs-up.
How hard would it be
to get a camera
on the inside
of this box screen?
JAMES: Great idea.
Okay, good.
We're gonna have to do
a really quick transition
with Trevor
to hand him the guitars.
Right. Can we just look at that
real quick from back there?
I think that's a good frame.
And then basically
the screen goes white,
then that lights up blue.
And then it opens
and then I jump down
through it.
That, we've never seen that.
Yeah.
So, Billie, show us
what you're gonna do.
And...
Okay. Great. Perfect.
If you do that, Cole will
cover you dropping down.
Billie, I think we have this.
JAMES: It's your show.
It's your creative vision.
It's gonna say,
"Directed by Billie Eilish...
with James Cameron."
(LAUGHTER)
(SINGSONGY) Can't wait.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(CHEERING, WHOOPING)
AUDIENCE (CHANTING):
Billie! Billie!
Billie! Billie! Billie!
(CHEERING, CHANTING FADES)
(CHEERING RISES)
How you doing?
(DELIGHTED SCREAMING)
You want to have some fun?
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
("WILDFLOWER" PLAYS)
♪ Things fall apart ♪
♪ And time breaks your heart ♪
♪ I wasn't there ♪
♪ But I know ♪
♪ She was your girl ♪
♪ You showed her the world ♪
♪ But fell out of love ♪
♪ And you both let go ♪
♪ She was cryin'
On my shoulder ♪
♪ All I could do was hold her ♪
♪ It only made us closer ♪
(SINGING ALONG SHAKILY)
♪ Until July ♪
♪ Now, I know
That you love me ♪
♪ You don't need to remind me ♪
♪ I should put it all
Behind me ♪
♪ Shouldn't I ♪
♪ But I see her ♪
♪ In the back of my mind ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ Like a fever ♪
♪ Like I'm burning alive ♪
♪ Like a sign ♪
♪ Did I cross the line? ♪
(SOBBING)
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
Everybody,
keep those lights up for me.
(CHEERING)
♪ Well, good things
Don't last ♪
♪ Good things don't last ♪
♪ And life moves so fast ♪
♪ Life moves so fast ♪
♪ But I'd never ask ♪
♪ Who was better ♪
♪ I'd never ask ♪
♪ 'Cause she couldn't be ♪
♪ Couldn't ♪
♪ More different from me ♪
♪ Different ♪
♪ Happy and free ♪
♪ In leather ♪
♪ And I know that you love me ♪
♪ You don't need to remind me ♪
♪ Wanna put it all
Behind me ♪
♪ But baby I see her ♪
♪ In the back of my mind ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ Feels like a fever ♪
♪ Like I'm burning alive ♪
♪ Like a sign ♪
♪ Did I cross ♪
♪ The line? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Valentine's Day
Cryin' in the hotel ♪
♪ I know you didn't mean
To hurt me ♪
♪ So I kept it to myself ♪
♪ And I wonder ♪
♪ Do you see her ♪
♪ In the back of your mind ♪
♪ In my eyes? ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
AUDIENCE: ♪ You say
No one knows you so well ♪
♪ But every time you touch me
I just wonder how she felt ♪
♪ Valentine's Day
Cryin' in the hotel ♪
♪ I know you didn't mean
To hurt me ♪
♪ So I kept it to myself ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Okay.
This whole tour
I've been doing everything
I can not to get sick.
Because I knew
something would happen.
Something bad.
Here she is.
Classic, good old-fashioned
Billie sprain.
But it's not that bad.
It is not that bad.
I'm supposed to be
walking on it,
so I just have these here...
WOMAN: For sympathy?
For sympathy. (LAUGHING) Yeah.
WOMAN:
Good.
(STRAINS GOOFILY)
JAMES: You know, and if you're
ever gonna sprain your ankle,
do it the night before
the movie starts filming.
Why not? Why the fork not?
By the way,
this is the sprained ankle.
I get taped on my ankles
every show.
This is every single show.
But before this
even happened, I--
my shins have been hurting
for months.
JAMES:
You told me when we first met
that you carried a lot
of pain with you
throughout the tour.
Yes, correct.
JAMES:
So this is just more of that.
BILLIE: This is just more
of what I-- You know...
What are you gonna do?
Could be worse.
And then, um,
while she does this,
I call my vocal coach, Doug,
on FaceTime.
It's gonna be loud,
just so you know.
(VOCALIZING IN SCALES)
Let's add
the little figure 8 nose to it.
(VOCALIZING IN SCALES)
DOUG: Beautiful.
(VOCALIZING)
(GARGLING)
(SINGING ALPHABET
IN SCALES)
I'm good.
I'm my own makeup artist,
and hair, on these tours.
I've learned that doing that
with eyeliner
makes the line
even sharper than--
It really reads
from a distance.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Okay, so...
(CHEERING FADES)
(BILLIE CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
For this next song...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm gonna be using a loop
on my voice
and singing this little...
stack of harmonies.
FAN: I love you!
Um, and the thing is, that
for this thing to work,
the room has to be
completely silent
for the duration
of using this loop.
And it's the only time
in the whole show
that I'll ask for silence,
because you know
how much I love all the noise
and all the things you
always do that I love so much.
Um.
But for one minute
we have to be very, very,
very, very quiet. Okay?
(CHEERING)
(AUDIENCE SHUSHING)
Okay.
Shh...
♪ Hmm-hmm ♪
(VOCALS LAYERING)
(LOOPED VOCALS PLAYING)
♪ Hmm-hmm ♪
♪ Don't you know
I'm no good for you? ♪
♪ I've learned to lose you
Can't afford to ♪
FAN: Love you!
FAN 2: I love you!
♪ Tore my shirt
To stop you bleedin' ♪
♪ But nothin' ever
Stops you leavin' ♪
♪ Quiet when I'm coming home ♪
♪ And I'm on my own ♪
FAN: Love you!
♪ I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
♪ I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
Very good.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ Too much already? ♪
♪ I'll only hurt you ♪
♪ If you let me ♪
♪ Call me friend ♪
♪ But keep me closer ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ Call me back ♪
♪ And I'll call you ♪
♪ When the party's over ♪
♪ Quiet when I'm coming home ♪
(SINGING ALONG SHAKILY)
♪ And I'm on my own ♪
♪ And I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
♪ Yeah, I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
♪ But nothin' is better
Sometimes ♪
♪ Once we've both said
Our goodbyes ♪
♪ Let's just let it go ♪
♪ Let me let you ♪
♪ Go ♪
(SNIFFLES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Quiet when
I'm coming home ♪
♪ And I'm on my own ♪
♪ I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
♪ I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
("THE DINER" PLAYS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS LOUDER)
♪ Don't be afraid of me ♪
♪ I'm what you need ♪
♪ I saw you on the screens ♪
♪ I know we're meant to be ♪
♪ You're starrin'
In my dreams ♪
♪ In magazines ♪
♪ You're lookin' right at me ♪
♪ I'm here around the clock ♪
♪ I'm waitin' on your block ♪
♪ But please don't
Call the cops ♪
♪ They'll make me stop ♪
♪ I just wanna talk ♪
♪ Bet I could save your life ♪
♪ You could be my wife ♪
♪ Could get into a fight ♪
♪ I'll say, "You're right" ♪
♪ And you'll kiss me
Goodnight ♪
♪ I waited on the corner
'Til I saw the sitter leave ♪
♪ Was easy getting over
And I landed on my feet ♪
♪ I came in through the kitchen
Lookin' for something to eat ♪
♪ I left a calling card so
They would know that it was ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ I tried to save you
But I failed ♪
(FAN SHRIEKS)
♪ Two fifty thousand dollar
Bail ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Two hundred
Fifty thousand dollar! ♪
♪ While I'm away
Don't read my mail ♪
♪ Just bring a veil ♪
♪ And come visit me in jail ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ Visit me in jail! ♪
♪ I'll go back to the diner ♪
♪ I'll write another letter ♪
♪ I hope you'll read it
This time ♪
♪ You better ♪
♪ The cops around the corner ♪
♪ Stopped me
When I tried to leave ♪
♪ They told me I was crazy ♪
♪ And they knocked me
Off my feet ♪
♪ They came in
Through the kitchen ♪
♪ Lookin' for something
Discreet ♪
♪ I left a calling card ♪
♪ So they would know
That it was ♪
♪ Me ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ That it was me ♪
♪ I memorized your number ♪
♪ Now I call you
When I please ♪
♪ I tried to end it all ♪
♪ But now I'm back up
On my feet ♪
♪ I saw you in the car ♪
♪ With someone else
And couldn't sleep ♪
♪ If somethin' happens to him ♪
♪ You can bet that it was me ♪
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
("ILOMILO" PLAYS, MUFFLED)
(WHISPERING) Wow.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
CREWMAN: Yeah, I got you.
♪ The world's a little blurry ♪
♪ Or maybe it's my eyes ♪
♪ The friends
I've had to bury ♪
♪ They keep me up at night ♪
♪ Said I couldn't
Love someone ♪
♪ 'Cause I might break ♪
♪ If you're gonna die ♪
♪ Not by mistake ♪
♪ So, where did you go? ♪
♪ I should know
But it's cold ♪
♪ And I don't wanna be lonely ♪
♪ So tell me you'll come home ♪
♪ Even if it's just a lie ♪
♪ I tried not to upset you ♪
♪ Let you rescue me ♪
♪ The day I met you ♪
♪ I just wanted
To protect you ♪
♪ But now I'll never get to ♪
♪ Hurry ♪
♪ I'm worried ♪
(CHEERING ERUPTS)
♪ Where did you go?
I should know, but it's cold ♪
♪ And I don't wanna be lonely ♪
♪ Was hoping you'd come home ♪
♪ I don't care if it's a lie ♪
("BAD GUY" PLAYING)
(AUDIENCE VOCALIZING
WITH BASSLINE)
♪ White shirt now red
My bloody nose ♪
♪ Sleepin'
You're on your tippy toes ♪
♪ Creepin'
Around like no one knows ♪
♪ Think you're so criminal ♪
♪ Bruises on both my knees
For you ♪
♪ Don't say thank you
Or please ♪
♪ I do what I want
When I'm wanting to ♪
♪ My soul
So cynical ♪
♪ So you're a tough guy
Like it really rough guy ♪
♪ Just can't get enough guy
Chest always so puffed guy ♪
♪ I'm that bad type
Make your mama sad type ♪
♪ Make your girlfriend
Mad tight ♪
♪ Might seduce your dad type ♪
(CAMERA CLATTERS)
♪ I'm the bad guy ♪
♪ Duh ♪
♪ I like it
When you take control ♪
♪ Even if you know
That you don't ♪
♪ Own me ♪
♪ I'll let you play the role ♪
♪ I'll be your animal ♪
♪ My mommy likes
To sing along with me ♪
♪ But she won't sing
This song ♪
♪ If she reads all the lyrics ♪
♪ She'll pity the men I know ♪
♪ So you're a ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Tough guy
Like it really rough guy ♪
♪ Just can't get enough guy ♪
♪ Chest always so puffed guy ♪
♪ I'm that bad type
Make your mama ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Sad type ♪
♪ Make your girlfriend ♪
♪ Mad tight ♪
♪ Might seduce your ♪
♪ Dad type ♪
♪ I'm the bad guy ♪
♪ Duh ♪
BILLIE:
♪ I'm the bad guy ♪
♪ I am ♪
♪ Duh ♪
♪ I'm only good at bein' bad ♪
♪ Bad ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ I like when you get mad ♪
♪ I guess I'm pretty glad ♪
♪ That you're alone ♪
♪ You said she's scared of me ♪
♪ I mean
I don't see what she sees ♪
♪ But maybe it's 'cause
I'm wearing your cologne ♪
♪ I'm a bad guy ♪
(EXHALES)
AUDIENCE: ♪ I am ♪
♪ I'm a bad guy ♪
♪ Bad guy ♪
(EXHALES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
JAMES:
Set the Wayback Machine to
I think your first show
of the tour was in Quebec,
is that right?
First show was in Quebec.
And Finneas sent you a text.
Yeah. He sent me flowers!
I didn't even read it,
and I'm gonna be--
(VOICE BREAKING)
I'm already crying.
BILLIE: "Almost seven years ago
to the day,
we started your first
headline tour of North America.
It's been the joy of my life
to travel the world with you
and watch you hold
every person
who comes to your shows
in the palm of your hand.
Good luck tonight,
but you don't need it.
No one does it like you do.
Can't wait to see you soon.
Love, Pinch."
(CHUCKLES)
BILLIE: Finneas was always
with me, no matter what.
That's the only way
we ever performed.
And so performing
without Finneas was, like,
completely a new region
that I just had never been in.
And very scary.
(SHAKILY) Yeah, this is gonna
be my first show, um,
ever without him.
So...
Miss you, Finneas.
("THE GREATEST" PLAYS)
Ugh!
♪ I'm trying my best ♪
♪ To keep you satisfied ♪
♪ Let you get your rest ♪
♪ While I stayed up all night ♪
♪ And you don't wanna know ♪
♪ How alone I've been ♪
♪ Let you come and go ♪
♪ Whatever state I'm in ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ My congratulations ♪
♪ All my love and patience ♪
♪ All my admiration ♪
♪ All the times I waited ♪
♪ For you to want me naked ♪
♪ Made it all look painless ♪
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ Hm, oh-oh ♪
♪ Hm ♪
♪ Doing what's right ♪
♪ Without a reward ♪
♪ And we don't have to fight ♪
♪ When it's not worth
Fighting for ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ You don't wanna know ♪
♪ Just what I would've done ♪
♪ Hm ♪
♪ Anything at all ♪
♪ Worse than anyone ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ And man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ My congratulations ♪
♪ All my love and patience ♪
♪ All my admiration ♪
♪ And all the times I waited ♪
♪ For you to want me naked ♪
♪ I made it all look painless ♪
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ The greatest ♪
♪ Ah-oh ♪
♪ I, I loved you ♪
♪ And I still do ♪
♪ Just wanted passion
From you ♪
♪ I just wanted
What I gave you ♪
♪ I waited ♪
♪ And waited ♪
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ God, I hate it ♪
♪ All my love and patience ♪
♪ Unappreciated ♪
♪ You said
Your heart was jaded ♪
♪ You couldn't even break it ♪
♪ I shouldn't have to say it ♪
♪ You could've been
The greatest ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
It's interesting, like,
the day of a show is, is--
for me, it just feels like
any day at all.
I just feel like I'm, like,
going to hang out
with my friends.
They might not really
even be able to see me.
No, they're seeing something.
If I'm having a bad day
or feeling,
you know,
frustrated or resentful or
annoyed that I have to play
a show, I'm like--
I always try to remember, like,
the kid at the top,
you know,
all the way at the top,
in the top row...
(CHEERING)
BILLIE: ...who's just been,
like, dying
for this day.
It is so crazy.
They've been here for days.
FAN: I've just been through it.
But with Billie by my side,
through all the trials
and tribulations...
Billie has given me
such confidence
to step out into the world
and the skin
that I have been blessed with.
I was going through
a dark time
throughout middle school
and high school.
I was actually going through
a really tough time in my life
because you know, hormones
and my puberty, and everything.
Just, I got bullied a lot
in middle school.
She's made my life,
like, so much better.
She's helped me
heal over things.
And it made me feel,
like, so much less alone.
It made me feel like
I had a safe space.
I was just, like,
heard and seen.
Without her music,
I wouldn't have connection
with my family, yep.
Let's see
if they get my notifications.
Oh, my gosh.
She's looking, she's looking.
Yeah.
Yeah, but she can't see anyone.
She's gonna go tell them.
Tell them!
FAN: Every time I did hear
that song, I felt like
she was there with me
singing it in my ears.
(CHUCKLES)
It just felt like she was
just always somebody there,
no matter what.
(BILLIE LAUGHING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
BILLIE: Oh-oh.
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
WOMAN: Oh.
BILLIE: Oh, my God.
(BILLIE GIGGLING)
Parents, therapy,
nothing could compare
to just how pure
those songs felt
and how they just
healed everything,
all the pain that I felt.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
She connected in such a way
that just, like,
nobody else could.
See that? Do you think
they can see that?
I wrote "I love you."
Do you think
they're gonna see that?
FAN: I'm just so grateful
to Billie and...
I love her so much and
it's, like, helping me so much.
She's made me realize,
like, like,
my mental health
can and will be okay.
Like, the only thing
that kept me going
and made me feel
like I was being heard and...
that was something
worth living for.
She just saves a lot of people,
and I'm grateful for that.
I can't explain.
She means everything to me.
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
(BILLIE GIGGLES)
Love you!
I have my dream
to see her one day,
and now today is that day.
And I'm so excited to see her.
Billie Eilish, y'all.
Like, you know what I mean?
Bye! (LAUGHS)
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
BILLIE: I feel, like, really
grateful that I have this...
way to be able to connect
with that many people
and, like, be that support
for so many people
all around the world,
in places where they might
not be able to be,
you know,
freely themselves or--
or feel
safe or seen or, you know...
cared for.
And I-- I feel so lucky
that I-- I get to do that.
Even in a small way, you know?
(CHEERS FADE IN)
(CHEERING)
Everyone on this right side
of the room,
are you doing good tonight?
(CHEERS, APPLAUSE)
Good.
What about at the end
of the room over there?
You good?
(CHEERS)
And what about at
that end of the room?
Are you good?
(CHEERS)
And what about
my left side of the room?
Are you good tonight?
(CHEERS)
Good.
Everyone, these are my friends
Ava and Jane.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Whoo!
This tour has been so wonderful
and beautiful and amazing,
and it's all because
of you guys.
Thank you for giving us
the privilege of coming here.
I've had such an amazing time
all over the world. Um...
It's been almost a year since
we've been doing this show.
Um, and it's just been
the coolest experience ever.
And, love you guys so much.
If you're in here,
if you're watching this,
you're safe here.
I love you and you're seen.
I hope you feel free
to be yourself
and comfortable and safe and--
Yeah, okay, bye.
("YOUR POWER" PLAYS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Oh-oh ♪
♪ Hm ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Try not to abuse your power ♪
♪ I know we didn't choose
To change ♪
♪ You might not wanna
Lose your power ♪
♪ But havin' it's so strange ♪
♪ She said ♪
♪ You were a hero ♪
♪ You played the part ♪
♪ But you ruined her
In a year ♪
♪ Don't act like it was hard ♪
♪ And you swear
You didn't know ♪
♪ Didn't know ♪
♪ No wonder
Why you didn't ask ♪
♪ She was sleepin'
In your clothes ♪
♪ In your clothes ♪
♪ But now she's got
To get to class ♪
♪ How dare you? ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ How dare you? ♪
♪ And how could you? ♪
♪ Will you only feel bad
When they find out ♪
♪ If you could
Take it all back ♪
♪ Would you? ♪
♪ Try not to abuse your power ♪
♪ I know we didn't choose
To change ♪
♪ You might not wanna
Lose your power ♪
♪ But havin' it's so strange ♪
♪ I thought
That I was special ♪
♪ You made me feel ♪
♪ Like it was my fault ♪
♪ You were the devil ♪
♪ Lost your appeal ♪
♪ Does it keep you in control ♪
♪ In control ♪
♪ For you to keep her
In a cage ♪
♪ And you swear
You didn't know ♪
♪ Didn't know ♪
♪ You said you thought
She was your age ♪
♪ How dare you? ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ How dare you? ♪
♪ And how could you? ♪
♪ Will you only feel bad
If it turns out ♪
♪ That they kill
Your contract ♪
♪ Would you? ♪
♪ Try not to abuse your power ♪
♪ I know we didn't choose
To change ♪
♪ You might not wanna
Lose your power ♪
♪ But power isn't pain ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Hmm, ooh ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(BILLIE MURMURING, SMOOCHES)
Hi. You are so precious.
God, Maisie,
this is ridiculous.
She is so precious,
I can't even believe it.
Guys, come in here.
Tour is so brutal
and so, like, taxing, and
I like to have a puppy room
for the guys to
kind of get to, like,
go chill and just have some
oxytocin that they get.
Serotonin, oxytocin.
JAMES:
Is this a normal thing for you
when you're in these towns?
Yeah, we try to,
wherever we go,
to have whatever rescue
organization is around
and available and willing
to bring the dogs
and puppies and babies
that need homes to the venue.
I have two rescues,
my mom has a rescue,
my brother has two rescues.
And multiple people on my crew
have adopted dogs
from tour, from my tour.
I'm doing this
on my next movie
for sure.
Yeah.
Everyone needs some--
some dog love.
("SKINNY" PLAYS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
♪ Hmm, hmm ♪
♪ I fell in love
For the first time ♪
♪ With a friend
It's a good sign ♪
♪ Feelin' off
When I feel fine ♪
♪ Twenty-one took a lifetime ♪
♪ People say I look happy ♪
♪ Just because I got skinny ♪
♪ But the old me is still me ♪
♪ And maybe the real me ♪
♪ And I think she's pretty ♪
(FAN WHOOPS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ And I still cry ♪
♪ Cry ♪
♪ And you know why ♪
♪ Am I acting my age now? ♪
♪ Am I already
On the way out? ♪
♪ When I step off the stage
I'm a bird in a cage ♪
♪ I'm a dog in a dog pound ♪
♪ And you said
I was your secret ♪
♪ And you didn't get
To keep it ♪
♪ And the Internet is hungry
For the meanest kind of funny ♪
♪ And somebody's
Gotta feed it ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Do you still cry? ♪
♪ Still cry ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Cry ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I never did you wrong ♪
♪ And my ♪
♪ My patience is gone ♪
♪ Is gone ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I never did you wrong ♪
♪ I loved you for so long ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(INSTRUMENTALS OF
"THE GREATEST" PLAYING)
FAN: We love you, Billie!
FAN 2: We love you!
Billie! Billie!
Billie! Billie! Billie!
Oh, my God!
(WEEPING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(PLAYING "TV")
♪ I don't wanna
Talk right now ♪
♪ I just wanna watch TV ♪
♪ I'll stay in the pool
And drown ♪
♪ So I don't have
To watch you leave ♪
♪ I put on Survivor ♪
♪ Just to watch
Somebody suffer ♪
♪ Maybe I should
Get some sleep ♪
♪ Sinking in the sofa ♪
♪ While they all
Betray each other ♪
♪ What's the point
Of anything? ♪
♪ All of my friends ♪
♪ Are missing again ♪
♪ That's what happens
When you fall in love ♪
♪ You don't have the time ♪
♪ You leave them all behind ♪
♪ You tell yourself "It's fine,
You're just in love" ♪
♪ I don't know
Where you are right now ♪
♪ Did you see me on TV? ♪
♪ I'll try not
To starve myself ♪
♪ Just because
You're mad at me ♪
♪ And I'll be in denial ♪
♪ For at least a little while ♪
♪ What about the plans
We made? ♪
♪ The Internet's gone wild ♪
♪ Watching movie stars
On trial ♪
♪ While they're ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ While they're ♪
♪ Overturning ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Overturning ♪
♪ Roe v. Wade ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Roe v. Wade ♪
♪ And now all of my friends ♪
♪ Are missing again ♪
♪ 'Cause that's what happens
When you fall in love ♪
♪ You don't have the time ♪
♪ You leave them all behind ♪
♪ And you tell yourself ♪
♪ "It's fine,
You're just in love" ♪
♪ And I don't get along ♪
♪ With anyone ♪
♪ Maybe I'm the problem ♪
AUDIENCE: No, you're not!
♪ Maybe I, maybe I ♪
♪ Maybe I'm the problem ♪
Sing with me.
♪ Maybe I, maybe I ♪
♪ Maybe I'm the problem ♪
Louder!
AUDIENCE:
♪ Maybe I, maybe I ♪
♪ Maybe I'm the problem ♪
♪ Baby, I, baby, I ♪
♪ Baby, I ♪
♪ Baby, I'm the problem ♪
♪ Baby, I, baby, I ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
JAMES:
I love the fact that
you're there singing,
one voice.
You don't have
a big bunch of
backup dancers
and all that stuff. It's you...
Yeah, it's basically just...
...and twenty thousand...
...me up there.
...of your--
Right?
Yup.
JAMES: And they are just
right with you.
You're like a tuning fork,
and they're hitting the same
beats exactly.
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
I wonder,
what does that feel like?
I mean, you make that happen,
so you must
kind of understand that.
But what does it feel like?
It's a really good
challenge for me because
it's kind of all on me.
And I've always felt this way
because
every time I've toured
it's basically just, like,
me running around
and jumping.
And that comes from,
you know, my love for rap
and hip-hop and how
those were my favorite
performers when I was younger.
I just wanted
the freedom of being
a guy on stage,
you know, shirtless,
running around, jumping.
And the whole crowd
is just, like, in awe
of this one person on stage,
able to make the entire room
jump and mosh and
I had never
seen a girl do that.
It's part of why I don't
want a bunch of people
on my stage.
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
Because I want to feel
like it's me
and them.
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
BILLIE:
And...
You love that.
I love that.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ Billie ♪
("BURY A FRIEND" PLAYS)
♪ What do you want from me? ♪
♪ Why don't you run from me? ♪
♪ What are you wondering? ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ Why aren't
You scared of me? ♪
♪ Why do you care for me? ♪
♪ When we all fall asleep ♪
♪ Where do we go? ♪
♪ Come here ♪
♪ Say it, spit it out ♪
♪ What is it exactly ♪
♪ You're payin'? ♪
♪ Is the amount
Cleanin' you out? ♪
♪ Am I satisfactory? ♪
♪ Today, I'm thinkin' about ♪
♪ The things that are deadly ♪
♪ The way
I'm drinkin' you down ♪
♪ Like I wanna drown
Like I wanna end me ♪
♪ Step on the glass ♪
♪ Staple your tongue ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Bury a friend ♪
♪ Try to wake up ♪
♪ Ah-ahh ♪
♪ Cannibal class
Killing the son ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Bury a friend ♪
♪ I wanna end me ♪
(DELIGHTED SQUEAL, CHEER)
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ End me ♪
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
AUDIENCE AND BACKING TRACK:
♪ What do you want from me? ♪
♪ Why don't you run from me? ♪
♪ What are you wondering? ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ Why aren't
You scared of me? ♪
♪ Why do you care for me? ♪
♪ When we all fall asleep ♪
♪ Where do we go? ♪
♪ Listen ♪
♪ Keep you in the dark ♪
♪ What had you expected? ♪
♪ Me to make you my art ♪
♪ Make you a star
And get you connected? ♪
♪ I'll meet you in the park ♪
♪ I'll be calm and collected ♪
♪ But we knew
Right from the start ♪
♪ That you'd fall apart
'Cause I'm too expensive ♪
♪ It's probably somethin'
That shouldn't be ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ Said out loud ♪
♪ Honestly
I thought that I would be ♪
♪ Dead by now ♪
♪ Wow ♪
♪ Calling security
Keepin' my head held down ♪
♪ Bury the hatchet
Or bury a friend right now ♪
♪ The debt I owe
Gotta sell my soul ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't say no ♪
♪ No, I can't say no ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ Then my limbs all froze ♪
♪ And my eyes won't close ♪
♪ And I can't say no ♪
♪ I can't say no ♪
♪ Careful ♪
♪ Step on the glass ♪
♪ Staple your tongue
Ahh ♪
♪ Bury a friend ♪
♪ Try to wake up ♪
♪ Ah-ahh ♪
♪ Cannibal class ♪
♪ Killing the son ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ Bury a friend ♪
♪ I wanna end me ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
♪ End me ♪
("OXYTOCIN" PLAYS)
Everybody on your feet
right now!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Jump!
♪ Can't take it back
Once it's been set in motion ♪
♪ You know I love
To rub it in like lotion ♪
♪ If you only pray on Sunday ♪
♪ Could you come my way
On Monday ♪
♪ 'Cause I like to do things ♪
♪ God doesn't approve of ♪
♪ If She saw us ♪
♪ She couldn't look away ♪
♪ Look away, look away ♪
♪ She'd wanna get involved ♪
♪ Involved, involved ♪
♪ And what would people say ♪
♪ People say, people say ♪
♪ If they listen
Through the wall ♪
♪ The wall, the wall ♪
♪ I can see it clear as day ♪
♪ You don't really
Need a break ♪
♪ Wanna see what you can take ♪
♪ You should really run away ♪
Come on!
♪ I wanna do
Bad things to you ♪
♪ I wanna make you yell ♪
♪ I wanna do
Bad things to you ♪
♪ Don't wanna treat you well ♪
Everybody in this room,
I need you to get down
as low as you possibly
can get right now.
Get low.
All the way
to the top of the room.
Down.
(CHEERS)
Lower.
Here we go.
One, two...
One, two, three, jump!
♪ I wanna do
Bad things to you ♪
♪ I wanna make you yell ♪
♪ I wanna do
Bad things to you ♪
♪ Don't wanna treat you well ♪
♪ I wanna do
Bad things to you ♪
(MUFFLED)
♪ I wanna make you yell ♪
♪ Gonna do bad things to you ♪
♪ Don't wanna treat you well ♪
(AUDIENCE SCREAMING)
♪ Bad things ♪
♪ I can see it clear as day ♪
♪ You don't really need
A break ♪
♪ Wanna see what you can take ♪
♪ You should really run away ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
CHARLI: Hey, Billie,
are you there?
("GUESS" BY CHARLI XCX
FEATURING BILLIE EILISH PLAYS)
♪ You wanna guess
The color of my underwear ♪
♪ You wanna know what I got
Goin' on down there ♪
♪ Is it pretty in pink ♪
♪ Or all see-through ♪
♪ Is it showin' off
My brand-new ♪
♪ Lower-back tattoo? ♪
♪ You wanna put 'em
In your mouth ♪
♪ Pull 'em all down south ♪
♪ You wanna
Turn this shit out ♪
♪ That's what
I'm talkin' about ♪
♪ Pu-pu-pu-put 'em
In your mouth ♪
♪ Pull 'em all down south ♪
♪ You wanna
Turn this shit out ♪
♪ That's what I'm talkin' about
Yeah ♪
♪ Try it, bite it
Lick it, spit it ♪
♪ Pull it to the side
And get all up in it ♪
♪ Wear 'em, post 'em
Might remix it ♪
♪ Send 'em to The Dare
Yeah, I think he's with it ♪
♪ Try it, bite it
Lick it, spit it ♪
♪ Pull it to the side
And get all up in it ♪
Four, three, two, one.
♪ It's so delicious ♪
(SPEED LIFT RUMBLES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
♪ Work it out ♪
♪ Don't have to guess ♪
♪ The color of your underwear ♪
♪ Already know
What you've got ♪
♪ Goin' on down there ♪
♪ It's that lacy black pair
With the little bows ♪
♪ The ones I picked out
For you in Tokyo ♪
♪ I saw them
When you sat down ♪
♪ They were peekin' out ♪
♪ I'm gonna
Tell you right now ♪
♪ They're all
I'm thinkin' about ♪
♪ I wanna try it, bite it
Lick it, spit it ♪
♪ Pull it to the side
And get all up in it ♪
♪ Kiss it, ride it
Can I fit it ♪
♪ Charli likes boys
But she knows I'd hit it ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Go crazy with me, come on!
AUDIENCE: ♪ Charli, call me
If you're with it ♪
♪ Yeah, guess, guess
Guess, guess ♪
♪ Guess, guess, guess, guess ♪
♪ Guess, guess,
Guess, guess, guess ♪
CHARLI: ♪ You wanna guess
What me and Billie ♪
♪ Have been textin' about? ♪
♪ We've been disrespectful ♪
CHARLI: ♪ Still tryin' to guess
The password ♪
♪ To my Google Drive ♪
♪ Are you obsessed with me? ♪
♪ You wanna guess the address ♪
♪ Of the party we're at ♪
♪ You know
you're not invited ♪
CHARLI: ♪ You wanna guess
If we're serious ♪
♪ About this song ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
("EVERYTHING I WANTED" PLAYS)
♪ I had a dream ♪
♪ I got everything I wanted ♪
♪ Not what you'd think ♪
♪ And if I'm bein' honest ♪
♪ It might've been
A nightmare ♪
♪ To anyone who might care ♪
♪ Thought I could fly ♪
♪ So I stepped off the Golden ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ But nobody cried ♪
♪ Nobody even noticed ♪
♪ I saw them
Standing right there ♪
♪ I kinda thought
They might care ♪
♪ I had a dream ♪
♪ I got everything I wanted ♪
♪ But when I wake up
I see ♪
♪ You with me ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ You with me ♪
♪ And you say ♪
♪ "As long as I'm here ♪
♪ No one can hurt you ♪
♪ Don't wanna lie here ♪
♪ But you can learn to ♪
♪ If I could change ♪
♪ The way
That you see yourself ♪
♪ You wouldn't wonder
Why you hear ♪
♪ 'They don't deserve you'" ♪
♪ If I knew it all then
Would I do it again? ♪
♪ Would I do it again? ♪
♪ If they knew what they said ♪
♪ Would go straight
To my head ♪
♪ What would
They say instead? ♪
♪ If I knew it all then ♪
♪ Would I do it again? ♪
♪ If they knew what they said ♪
♪ Would go straight
To my head ♪
♪ What would
They say instead? ♪
(EXCITED SHOUTS)
FAN: Billie!
FAN 2: I love you, Billie!
FAN 3: Billie! Billie! Billie!
(CHEERING FADES)
Do you see the scrapes
on my hands?
That is from the fans.
JAMES: Is that from them?
I mean, they literally--
Oh, yeah, it looks bad.
Oh yeah, this is-- this
isn't even the worst of it.
I come from being that fan,
so...
to me...
I'm like...
I-- I understand that,
like, need and the desperation.
If I, when I was younger,
had gotten
up close to anyone
that I was a big fan of,
I can't even imagine
how that would have been.
I can't imagine
what I would have done.
And that's kind of why
I have so much...
empathy for it
and why I do it.
Because I feel like I...
(GASPS, LAUGHS)
I want to be the artist that
I would want to be a fan of.
("BLUE" PLAYS)
FAN: Billie!
♪ Don't know what's in store ♪
♪ Open up the door ♪
♪ In the back of my mind ♪
♪ I'm still overseas ♪
What?
♪ A bird in a cage
Thought you were made for me ♪
♪ I try ♪
Yes!
♪ But I'm so blue ♪
♪ But I'm not what you need ♪
♪ I'd like ♪
♪ To mean it when I say
I'm over you ♪
♪ But that's still not true ♪
♪ True ♪
♪ And I'm still so blue ♪
♪ And it's not true ♪
♪ I'm true blue, true blue ♪
♪ I'm true blue ♪
♪ Mm ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
("LOVELY" PLAYS)
♪ Oh, I hope someday ♪
♪ I'll make it out of here ♪
♪ Even if it takes all night ♪
♪ Or a hundred years ♪
♪ Need a place to hide ♪
♪ But I can't find one near ♪
♪ Wanna feel alive ♪
♪ Outside I can't fight
My fear ♪
♪ Isn't it lovely all alone ♪
♪ Heart made of glass ♪
♪ My mind of stone ♪
♪ Tear me to pieces ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS WILDLY)
♪ Skin to bone ♪
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Welcome home ♪
(GIGGLES)
Ah!
(CHEERS)
FAN: I love you!
Surprise!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(PLAYING
"IDONTWANNABEYOUANYMORE")
FAN: We love you, Finneas!
♪ Ba-da-da-da-da ♪
FAN: Love you, Finneas!
(AUDIENCE VOCALIZES)
♪ Don't be that way ♪
♪ Fall apart twice a day ♪
♪ I just wish ♪
♪ You could feel what you say ♪
♪ Show ♪
♪ Never tell ♪
♪ But I know you too well ♪
♪ Got a mood ♪
♪ That you wish
You could sell ♪
♪ If teardrops
Could be bottled ♪
♪ There'd be swimming pools
Filled by models ♪
♪ Told, "A tight dress ♪
♪ Is what makes you a whore" ♪
♪ If "I love you" ♪
♪ Was a promise ♪
♪ Would you break it ♪
♪ If you're honest ♪
♪ Tell the mirror ♪
♪ What you know
She's heard before ♪
FAN: We love you, guys!
♪ I don't wanna be you ♪
♪ Ahh-ooh ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
My brother, Finneas.
(PLAYING "OCEAN EYES")
♪ Hmm-hmm-hmm ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
♪ I've been watchin' you ♪
♪ For some time ♪
♪ I can't stop starin' ♪
♪ At those ocean eyes ♪
♪ Burning cities ♪
♪ And napalm skies ♪
♪ Fifteen flares inside ♪
♪ Your ocean eyes ♪
♪ Those ocean eyes ♪
♪ No fair ♪
♪ You really know
How to make me cry ♪
♪ When you give me
Those ocean eyes ♪
♪ I'm scared ♪
♪ I've never-- ♪
♪ Fallen from
Quite this high ♪
♪ Fallin' into
Your ocean eyes ♪
♪ Those ocean eyes ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da
Da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Ba-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ No fair ♪
♪ You really know
How to make me cry ♪
♪ When you give me
Those ocean eyes ♪
♪ Those ocean ♪
♪ Eyes ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(INAUDIBLE)
("L'AMOUR DE MA VIE" PLAYS)
♪ It isn't asking for a lot ♪
♪ For an apology ♪
♪ For making me feel like
It'd kill you ♪
♪ If I tried to leave ♪
♪ You said you'd never
Fall in love again ♪
♪ Because of me ♪
♪ Then you moved on ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ You wanted to keep it ♪
♪ Like somethin' you found ♪
♪ 'Til you didn't need it ♪
♪ But you should've seen it ♪
♪ The way it went down ♪
♪ You wouldn't believe it ♪
♪ Wanna know what I told her ♪
♪ With her hand
On my shoulder ♪
♪ You were so mediocre ♪
♪ And we're so glad it's over ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ It's over now ♪
♪ Camera ♪
♪ Caught on camera ♪
♪ The girls on camera ♪
♪ Your girl's a fan of ♪
♪ And you miss me ♪
♪ Say you miss me ♪
♪ It's such a pity ♪
♪ We're both so pretty ♪
Come on! Dance!
♪ I wanna know ♪
♪ Where did it go ♪
♪ I couldn't tell ♪
♪ I couldn't see ♪
♪ You weren't around ♪
♪ I was alone ♪
♪ You never once
Took care of me ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ You wanted to keep it ♪
♪ But you didn't try ♪
♪ Guess you didn't mean it ♪
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ Maybe your secret ♪
♪ Is you're just a guy ♪
♪ That couldn't complete it ♪
♪ Never got that Ferrari ♪
♪ Never dance at the party ♪
♪ I bet it's still mediocre ♪
♪ I'm just happy it's over ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ It's over now ♪
♪ Over now ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I wanna know ♪
♪ Where did it go? ♪
♪ I couldn't tell ♪
♪ I couldn't see ♪
♪ You weren't around ♪
♪ I was alone ♪
♪ You never once
Took care of me ♪
♪ Wanna know
It's not that complicated ♪
♪ I wasn't satiated ♪
♪ You weren't that bad
Just lazy ♪
♪ Too self-obsessed
To save me ♪
♪ It's not that complicated ♪
♪ I wasn't satiated ♪
♪ You're looking older lately ♪
♪ Dating another baby ♪
♪ Another baby ♪
(SCREAMS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Everyone, I want you to make
so much noise
for my incredible band
right here.
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
This is Andrew Marshall.
This is Solo Smith.
This is Abe Nouri.
This is Tom Crouch.
And my singers,
Ava and Jane Horner.
JAMES: It's your energy that
your fans are responding to.
And I was just thinking about
something you said
a second ago about how you--
you figured out
how to take that power
and make it a woman
on stage...
Yeah.
...who was doing these things
that you had seen men do.
Yep.
You've empowered yourself,
and then you're the
point person for all of them.
The truth is that,
as a young woman,
before all of this,
I loved performing more than
anything in the world, but
I didn't feel sexy
feeling feminine or--
or, you know,
showing more of my body,
and I felt like,
as a performer,
that was the only way that a
woman was able to be desirable.
I still
have that same feeling
that I've always had of, like,
you know, I am not desirable
if I'm wearing this
because it's not girly
and it's not feminine,
it's not revealing, and--
How is that fair,
that I can't just wear things
that make me
feel comfortable...
without being attractive?
I still have that,
like, feeling.
JAMES: But you're you.
But I'm me.
("WHAT WAS I MADE FOR?" PLAYS)
♪ I used to float ♪
♪ Now I just fall down ♪
♪ I used to know ♪
♪ But I'm not sure now ♪
♪ What I was made for ♪
FAN: I love you!
♪ What was I made for? ♪
♪ Takin' a drive ♪
♪ I was an ideal ♪
♪ Looked so alive ♪
♪ Turns out I'm not real ♪
♪ Just somethin' you paid for ♪
(FANS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
♪ What was I made for? ♪
♪ 'Cause I ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I don't know how to feel ♪
♪ But I wanna try ♪
(FANS CALLING OUT)
♪ I don't know how to feel ♪
♪ But someday ♪
♪ I might ♪
♪ Someday, I might ♪
I love you!
(FANS YELLING "I LOVE YOU")
♪ When did it end? ♪
♪ All the enjoyment ♪
♪ I'm sad again ♪
♪ But don't tell my boyfriend ♪
♪ It's not what he's made for ♪
♪ What was I made for? ♪
(FANS CALLING OUT, CHEERING)
♪ 'Cause I ♪
♪ I don't know how to feel ♪
♪ But I wanna try ♪
You sing it!
AUDIENCE:
♪ I don't know how to feel ♪
♪ But someday ♪
♪ I might ♪
♪ Someday, I might ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
♪ Think I forgot ♪
♪ How to be happy ♪
♪ Somethin' I'm not ♪
♪ But somethin' I can be ♪
♪ Somethin' I wait for ♪
♪ Somethin' I'm made for ♪
(FANS CRYING OUT INDISTINCTLY)
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
As women, we feel like
we have to do the thing
that society, or whatever,
want us to do.
And I just want to show
these young girls
that you don't have to do that
to be beautiful
and to be feminine or
just a woman.
I feel really proud and happy
for the young girls
that grow up now and
don't feel those eyes
on them, you know,
judging them for wearing
those kinds
of clothes, like me.
("HAPPIER THAN EVER" PLAYS)
♪ When I'm away from you ♪
♪ I'm happier than ever ♪
♪ Wish I could
Explain it better ♪
♪ I wish it wasn't true ♪
♪ Give me a day or two ♪
♪ To think of
Something clever ♪
♪ To write myself a letter ♪
♪ To tell me what to do ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
(FAN SHRIEKING)
♪ You call me again ♪
♪ Drunk in your Benz ♪
♪ Drivin' home
Under the influence ♪
♪ You scared me to death ♪
♪ But I'm wastin' my breath ♪
♪ 'Cause you only listen
To your fuckin'-- ♪
♪ I don't relate to you ♪
♪ I don't relate to you, no ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd never treat me
This shitty ♪
♪ You made me hate this city ♪
♪ And I don't talk shit
About you on the Internet ♪
♪ Never told anyone
Anything bad ♪
♪ 'Cause that shit's
Embarrassing ♪
♪ You were my everything ♪
♪ And all that you did
Was make me fuckin' sad ♪
♪ So don't waste the time
I don't have ♪
♪ And don't try
To make me feel bad ♪
♪ I could talk about
Every time ♪
♪ That you showed up on time ♪
♪ But I'd have an empty line ♪
♪ 'Cause you never did ♪
♪ Never paid any mind ♪
♪ To my mother or friends ♪
♪ So I shut 'em all out
For you ♪
♪ 'Cause I was a kid ♪
♪ You ruined everything good ♪
♪ You always said
You were misunderstood ♪
♪ You made all my moments
Your own ♪
♪ Just fuckin' leave me alone ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
("BIRDS OF A FEATHER" PLAYS)
This is my last song.
I love you so much!
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Till I'm in the grave ♪
♪ Until I rot away ♪
♪ Dead and buried ♪
♪ Till I'm in
The casket you carry ♪
♪ If you go, I'm goin' too ♪
Uh-huh.
♪ 'Cause it was always you ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ And if I'm turnin' blue ♪
♪ Please don't save me ♪
♪ Nothin' left to lose
Without my baby ♪
Sing!
♪ Birds of a feather
We should stick together ♪
♪ I know I said I'd never think
I wasn't better alone ♪
♪ Can't change the weather
Might not be forever ♪
♪ But if it's forever
It's even better ♪
♪ And I don't know
What I'm cryin' for ♪
♪ I don't think I could
Love you more ♪
♪ It might not be long
But baby, I ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ I'll love you
Till the day that I die ♪
♪ Till the day that I die ♪
♪ Till the light
Leaves my eyes ♪
♪ Till the day that I die ♪
♪ I want you to see ♪
Uh-huh.
♪ How you look to me ♪
(VOCALIZES)
♪ You wouldn't believe ♪
♪ If I told ya ♪
♪ You would keep
The compliments
I throw ya ♪
♪ But you're so full of-- ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Shit! ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
♪ Tell me it's a bit ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Say you don't see it ♪
♪ Your mind's polluted ♪
♪ Say you wanna quit ♪
♪ Don't be stupid ♪
AUDIENCE:
♪ And I don't know what ♪
♪ I'm cryin' for ♪
♪ I don't think I could
Love you more ♪
♪ It might not be long
But baby, I ♪
Everybody!
♪ Don't wanna say goodbye ♪
♪ Till the day that I die ♪
♪ Till the light ♪
♪ Can't change ♪
♪ Leaves my eyes ♪
♪ The weather ♪
♪ Might not be forever ♪
♪ Till the day that I die ♪
♪ But if it's forever
It's even better ♪
♪ I knew you in another life ♪
♪ You had that same look
In your eyes ♪
♪ I love you
Don't act so surprised ♪
My brother, Finneas, everybody!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Thank you so much
for having me.
I love you so much!
Have a good night!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
("BLUE" PLAYS)
♪ But they could say the same
About me ♪
♪ I sleep about
Three hours each night ♪
♪ Means only twenty-one
A week now ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ And I could say the same
About you ♪
♪ Born blameless
Grew up famous too ♪
♪ Just a baby
Born blue now ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
("MALE FANTASY" PLAYING)
(SOBBING) Oh, my God.
(SOBBING LAUGH)
JAMES:
So, how did you like the show?
It was so good.
(SOBBING)
I love Billie so much.
(DISTANT CHEERING)
(CHEERING GROWS LOUDER)
Bye bye!
FAN: We love you, Billie!
FAN 2: We love you!
FAN 3:
We love you! Billie!
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
FAN 4:
We love you so much!
♪ I used to know ♪
(LAUGHING)
(FANS YELLING)
Really fun! (LAUGHS)
♪ We'd get along
But it wasn't so ♪
(FANS CHEERING)
♪ And it's all I think about ♪
♪ When I'm behind the wheel ♪
♪ I worry this is ♪
JAMES: Wow.
Isn't that a thrill?
That's got to be a rush.
Oh...
FAN: Billie!
FAN 2: Love you!
(BILLIE LAUGHING)
Yeah.
I literally love that.
(FANS CHEERING)
BILLIE:
I never used to leave
the hotel
except to go to the venue.
And so these drives would be
the only time I would,
like, smell fresh air.
(WIND WHISTLING)
("L'AMOUR DE MA VIE" PLAYING)
♪ And we're so glad it's over ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ It's over now ♪
♪ Camera ♪
♪ Caught on camera ♪
♪ The girls on camera ♪
♪ Your girl's a fan of ♪
("BITTERSUITE" PLAYING)
♪ I can't fall in love ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ No matter how bad ♪
♪ I want to ♪
("LUNCH" PLAYS)
♪ I could eat that girl
For lunch ♪
♪ Yeah, she dances
On my tongue ♪
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
♪ And I could
Never get enough ♪
♪ I could buy her
So much stuff ♪
♪ It's a craving
Not a crush, huh ♪
♪ "Call me when you're there" ♪
♪ Said, "I bought you
Somethin' rare ♪
♪ And I left it under
'Claire'" ♪
♪ So now she's comin' up
The stairs ♪
♪ So I'm pullin' up a chair ♪
♪ And I'm puttin' up my hair ♪
♪ I could eat that girl
For lunch ♪
♪ Yeah, she dances
On my tongue ♪
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
♪ And I could
Never get enough ♪
♪ I could buy her
So much stuff ♪
♪ It's a craving
Not a crush, huh ♪
♪ I could ♪
♪ Eat that girl for lunch ♪
♪ I should ♪
♪ Tastes like
She might be the one ♪
("THE GREATEST" FADES IN)
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ My congratulations ♪
♪ All my love and patience ♪
♪ All my admiration ♪
♪ All the times I waited ♪
♪ For you to want me naked ♪
♪ Made it all look painless ♪
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ The greatest ♪
♪ Oh-oh ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I loved you ♪
♪ And I still do ♪
♪ Just wanted
Passion from you ♪
♪ Just wanted what I gave you ♪
♪ I waited ♪
♪ And waited ♪
♪ Man, am I the greatest? ♪
♪ God, I hate it ♪
♪ All my love and patience ♪
♪ Unappreciated ♪
♪ You said your heart
Was jaded ♪
♪ You couldn't even break it ♪
♪ I shouldn't have to say it ♪
♪ You could've been
The greatest ♪